Karim Gamal

Architect &Interior Designer

- Gkarim444@gmail.com
- 01067190256
- © Egypt, Menoufia, Menouf
- 9th July 1992
- Married **@**
- Facebook Profile
- Final Exemption
- Instgram Profile

Skills

AutoCAD 2D

Revit Architecture

3DS Max & Vray

Adobe Photoshop

Microsoft Office



Languages

Arabic

English



Personal Information

Architect with 9 years of experience in planning, building construction and implementation. I have experience in handling multiple projects at the same time and completing them in record time. Good experience in dealing with clients and companies

Education

Menoufia University, Bachelor of Architecture 2010 – 2015 | Shibin El Kom, Egypt

- Overall rating: 72.5% Very good
- Graduation project: very good

Professional Experience

Founder and Owner of Arcala Engineering Consultancy

2017 – present | Sadat City, Egypt Arcala Page on Facebook ≥

Architect Engineer at Engineering Consulting Office

July 2016 - December 2016 | Menouf, Egypt

Architect Engineer at General Contracting Company

July 2015 – July 2016 | Menouf, Egypt